

# **CONTACT**

Phone:

+91 63836 95963

Email:

prakashmpbe@gmail.com

Address:

2/179a, Mollappanahalli (village), Kovilur (post), Karimangalam (Tk), Dharmapuri (Dt), Pin: 635205.

### **EDUCATION**

B.E Computer Science
Jayalakshmi Institute of Technology,
Thoppur. Year of 2017-2020

DIPLOMA Computer Science Sri Moogambigai Polytechnic College, Palacode. Year of 2015-2017

### **PRO SKILLS**

Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe XD, Figma
Invision, Canva
Adobe Premier Pro
Wondershare Filmora

LANGUAGE

English, Tamil

**SOCIAL LINK** 

www.behance.net/techtake

# PRAKASH M

UI/UX DESIGNER

## **PROFILE**

Hi there, I'm a UI/UX designer passionate about creating simple and meaningful visual experiences. I like to solve problems by designing solutions. Through my work, I create interface that are both beautiful and functional. I am excited to explore new opportunities & gain experience in a challenging environment to expand my knowledge & skills.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

Batechnology UI/UX Designer
Chennai From 2022 - Present

I completed several projects, including the design of an ecommerce webapp, mobile to do list app, wireframes and improved ux for admin panel. Worked cross - functionally to deliver to 95% client satisfaction.

Min-Zharge UI/UX Designer
Salem From 2021 - 2022

Redesigned the website and decrease the bounce rate. Developed prototypes, website design, website redesign, by analysis.

Bluepearls Digital

Graphic & UI/UX Designer

Info From 2020 - 2021
Dharmapuri Created and maintai

Created and maintained ui standards for 20+ websites which included over 100 pages. Worked crossfunctionality with developers to implement new features

and maintain site usability.

## **PROJECT**

Designed and launched 12+ Apps like, Splink Sports, BCI App, E-Sankalp, etc. And also designed and lanched more than 12 website and 10+ admin panels like Consumer Connections, Thanigai, Radypay admin panel etc. Supported more than 10+ UI designs.

### **DESIGN SKILLS**

UI Design, Wire farming, Prototyping Design System, Android design Google material 3 design, UX Design, User research, User persona, User flow, Task flow, Information architecture, Empathy mapping Usability Testing, Heuristic evaluation.